[
  {
    "question": "Familia",
    "answer": "Family"
  },
  {
    "question": "Viaje",
    "answer": "Trip"
  },
  {
    "question": "Montañas",
    "answer": "Mountains"
  },
  {
    "question": "Clima",
    "answer": "Weather"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sol",
    "answer": "Sun"
  },
  {
    "question": "Coche",
    "answer": "Car"
  },
  {
    "question": "Borde del bosque",
    "answer": "Forest edge"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mochila",
    "answer": "Backpack"
  },
  {
    "question": "Prados",
    "answer": "Meadows"
  },
  {
    "question": "Flores",
    "answer": "Flowers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fotos",
    "answer": "Photos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Caminata",
    "answer": "Hike"
  },
  {
    "question": "Horas",
    "answer": "Hours"
  },
  {
    "question": "Estacionamiento",
    "answer": "Parking lot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Madre",
    "answer": "Mother"
  },
  {
    "question": "Policía",
    "answer": "Police"
  },
  {
    "question": "Niños",
    "answer": "Children"
  },
  {
    "question": "Banco",
    "answer": "Bench"
  },
  {
    "question": "Miedo",
    "answer": "Fear"
  },
  {
    "question": "Solución",
    "answer": "Solution"
  },
  {
    "question": "Oficiales de policía",
    "answer": "Police officers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Coche de policía",
    "answer": "Police car"
  },
  {
    "question": "Información",
    "answer": "Information"
  },
  {
    "question": "Robos de coches",
    "answer": "Car thefts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Taxi",
    "answer": "Taxi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Camino",
    "answer": "Path"
  },
  {
    "question": "Pueblo",
    "answer": "Village"
  },
  {
    "question": "Padres",
    "answer": "Parents"
  },
  {
    "question": "Llamada",
    "answer": "Call"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ciudad",
    "answer": "City"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ventana",
    "answer": "Window"
  },
  {
    "question": "Reparación",
    "answer": "Repair"
  },
  {
    "question": "Problema",
    "answer": "Problem"
  },
  {
    "question": "Seguro",
    "answer": "Insurance"
  },
  {
    "question": "hermoso",
    "answer": "beautiful"
  },
  {
    "question": "verde",
    "answer": "green"
  },
  {
    "question": "cansado",
    "answer": "tired"
  },
  {
    "question": "triste",
    "answer": "sad"
  },
  {
    "question": "nuevo",
    "answer": "new"
  },
  {
    "question": "tranquilo",
    "answer": "calm"
  },
  {
    "question": "inseguro",
    "answer": "unsure"
  },
  {
    "question": "lejos",
    "answer": "far"
  },
  {
    "question": "agotado",
    "answer": "exhausted"
  },
  {
    "question": "robado",
    "answer": "stolen"
  },
  {
    "question": "otro",
    "answer": "other"
  },
  {
    "question": "roto",
    "answer": "broken"
  },
  {
    "question": "feliz",
    "answer": "happy"
  },
  {
    "question": "bueno",
    "answer": "good"
  },
  {
    "question": "hacer",
    "answer": "to make"
  },
  {
    "question": "conducir",
    "answer": "to drive"
  },
  {
    "question": "brillar",
    "answer": "to shine"
  },
  {
    "question": "estacionar",
    "answer": "to park"
  },
  {
    "question": "ir",
    "answer": "to go"
  },
  {
    "question": "caminar",
    "answer": "to hike"
  },
  {
    "question": "tener",
    "answer": "to have"
  },
  {
    "question": "caminar",
    "answer": "to walk"
  },
  {
    "question": "ver",
    "answer": "to see"
  },
  {
    "question": "tomar",
    "answer": "to take"
  },
  {
    "question": "durar",
    "answer": "to last"
  },
  {
    "question": "ser/estar",
    "answer": "to be"
  },
  {
    "question": "buscar",
    "answer": "to search"
  },
  {
    "question": "creer",
    "answer": "to believe"
  },
  {
    "question": "robar",
    "answer": "to steal"
  },
  {
    "question": "llamar",
    "answer": "to call"
  },
  {
    "question": "llorar",
    "answer": "to cry"
  },
  {
    "question": "sentarse",
    "answer": "to sit"
  },
  {
    "question": "esperar",
    "answer": "to wait"
  },
  {
    "question": "proteger",
    "answer": "to protect"
  },
  {
    "question": "quedarse",
    "answer": "to stay"
  },
  {
    "question": "pensar",
    "answer": "to think"
  },
  {
    "question": "necesitar",
    "answer": "to need"
  },
  {
    "question": "ayudar",
    "answer": "to help"
  },
  {
    "question": "venir",
    "answer": "to come"
  },
  {
    "question": "preguntar",
    "answer": "to ask"
  },
  {
    "question": "parecer",
    "answer": "to look like"
  },
  {
    "question": "dar",
    "answer": "to give"
  },
  {
    "question": "escribir",
    "answer": "to write"
  },
  {
    "question": "decir",
    "answer": "to say"
  },
  {
    "question": "explicar",
    "answer": "to explain"
  },
  {
    "question": "suceder",
    "answer": "to happen"
  },
  {
    "question": "sentir",
    "answer": "to feel"
  },
  {
    "question": "traer",
    "answer": "to bring"
  },
  {
    "question": "quedarse dormido",
    "answer": "to fall asleep"
  },
  {
    "question": "hablar",
    "answer": "to speak"
  },
  {
    "question": "obtener",
    "answer": "to get"
  },
  {
    "question": "encontrar",
    "answer": "to find"
  },
  {
    "question": "estar de pie",
    "answer": "to stand"
  },
  {
    "question": "saber",
    "answer": "to know"
  },
  {
    "question": "pagar",
    "answer": "to pay"
  },
  {
    "question": "abrir",
    "answer": "to open"
  }
]